posirank.com 2019-01-30

# PosiRank - Privacy

### GENERAL INFORMATION - IP Addresses and Cookies

You may visit the Posirank site and will remain anonymous and will not be revealing any personal information. 

Our websites automatically log your IP address and domain name, and non-personal information such as the type of web browser you use, to help us administer the sites and to compile statistics such as the number of visitors. 

The Types of Cookies Posirank Uses (If we use more than session cookies, please add language for how our cookies work) 

Session cookies: These cookies are temporary and expire once you leave the site. Session cookies are mainly used by webshops to hold your items in the basket while you are shopping online. 

Posirank also permits third-party partners to use cookies and other technology to collect information about your browsing activities over time and across different websites when you use our site. Through a process called “retargeting,” each service places a cookie on your browser when you visit our site so that they can identify you and serve you ads on other sites around the web based on your browsing activity. 

**Submission of Personal Information**

If you choose to create a free account with Posirank, you will be required to submit some personal information, such as (but not limited to) your name and email address, before using the Posirank site. 

If you consent to provide your personal information by creating an account with Posirank, you may at any time withdraw your consent by contacting us at privacy at Posirank.com or at the address listed below. 

In order to make use of Posirank's services, you must provide us with the required personal data. If you do not to provide us with all the required information, it will not be possible to deliver Posirank products or services. 

Posirank retains the information you provide until such time that you request us to delete your information 

**Aggregation and Use of Anonymous Data**

Posirank aggregates information provided by you to create anonymous statistical and demographic data. This anonymous data helps Posirank better understand and know its customer base. That anonymous data may be provided to third parties but never in such a fashion as to identify you personally. Posirank uses Google Analytics for the collection of anonymous data. Learn more about how Google uses data collected using Google Analytics. 

The Google Analytics features that Posirank employs are as follows: 

_General Features related to browsing behavior such as: browser type/version and language, operating system type/version, device type/version, domains, page views, referring/exit pages, location data such as country, information about how you interact with our Site’s webpages and with third-party links, traffic and usage trends Demographics and Interest Reports: Age, Gender, Interest Data Advertising and Remarketing: This includes data from Google's signed-in users who have chosen to enable Google to associate their web and app browsing history with their Google account, and to use such information from their Google account to personalize ads User ID Tracking: To combine sessions across multiple devices and interactions for logged-in users Site Search Tracking: What a user typed into the sites search feature eCommerce Tracking: Information related to product purchased, price, date and time of purchase, order #, etc. Enhanced eCommerce Tracking: Information related to products viewed, products added/removed to cart, onsite promotions clicked, currency, refunds, etc._

You can opt out of Google Analytics by using this tool:  
<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

### Collected Information - Voluntary

PosiRank.com does not collect or obtain any personal or contact information about its users without their express, prior permission.

Users can, at their option, opt to join the PosiRank.com email newsletter. PosiRank.com uses a reputable, CAN-SPAM compliant newsletter management service. PosiRank.com only sends email communications to users who specifically request information about affiliate marketing or internet business.

If a user of the PosiRank website becomes a customer, then they will also be subscribed to the customer announcement list - which they can also unsubscribe from or manage from the PosiRank customer dashboard.

If a subscribed user wishes to unsubscribe from the newsletter for any reason, he or she may do so instantly by following the automated unsubscribe link, located in the footer of every email. In addition, the user may email us here, or by mail at:

PosiRank.com  
PosiRank LLC  
PO Box 475  
Glen Burnie, MD 21061

The data collected by our newsletter system will be used for marketing purposes related to topics on affiliate marketing, internet business or similarly relevant content.

The data will not be shared, sold, rented or distributed to any other party for any reason.

The only exception to this is if PosiRank.com is sold to a third-party, at which time data may be transferred to the new owner. Subscribed users will promptly be made aware of any such activity before any data is transferred, and will be given sufficient time to unsubscribe if they choose not to have their information transfered to the new ownership.

### Collected Information - Involuntary

PosiRank.com uses audience re-targeting technology to reach out to previous visitors, via traditional, non-invasive advertising, as they use other popular websites. This occurs when users load our website, and our re-targeting technology loads a tracking cookie onto the users browser.

To opt-out and unsubscribe from our re-targeting campaigns, all you have to do is clear any cookies associated with PosiRank.com, or our 3rd party advertising services, which may include ClickCertain, Adroll, and ReMarketingStats. For easy instructions on how to remove cookie files, please see this 3rd party tutorial.

The only additional information collected involuntarily from all visitors is basic geographic, referral, on-site navigation patterns and IP information for the purpose of tracking our website traffic statistics. We use this data in order to improve our website & user experience, as well as measuring the effectiveness of our advertising & marketing efforts.

Data is not evaluated on a "user by user" basis, but rather in the aggregate on a mass scale. We look at the overall patterns based on the statistical information collected from thousands of visitors.

The data is collected (and stored) by our preferred & reputable traffic analysis service. The data is stored securely and is not publicly available. Only PosiRank.com (ownership & staff) can access this statistical data, without exception.

This data is collected through the use of a simple javascript script on each page of PosiRank.com, and does not interfere with or affect the user's internet browsing program whatsoever.

PosiRank.com does NOT use spyware, viruses, trojans or otherwise any invasive, objectional methods to increase incoming traffic, or otherwise for any other purpose.
